{
  "vocabulary": {
    "beginner": {
      "section1": {
        "sectionDescription": "greetings",
        "questions": [
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which one of these is 'hello'?",
            "word": "salut",
            "options": ["bonjour", "oui", "merci", "salut"],
            "answer": "salut"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "Say 'Good morining' to Rhoda. __ Rhoda!",
            "word": "bonjour",
            "options": ["bonjour", "oui", "salut", "merci"],
            "answer": "bonjour"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which one of these is 'goodbye'?",
            "word": "au revoir",
            "options": ["merci", "oui", "au revoir", "salut"],
            "answer": "au revoir"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Select the correct meaning: 'goodnight'?",
            "word": "bonne nuit",
            "options": ["merci", "oui", "au revoir", "bonne nuit"],
            "answer": "bonne nuit"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "What do you hear?",
            "word": "bonsoir",
            "options": ["merci", "bonsoir", "au revoir", "salut"],
            "answer": "bonsoir"
          }
        ]
      },
     "section2": {
        "sectionDescription": "everydayWords",
        "questions": [
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "yes",
            "word": "oui",
            "options": ["oui", "nuit", "fille", "je"],
            "answer": "oui"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "__ suis Sam!",
            "word": "je",
            "options": ["tu", "nous", "vous", "ils"],
            "answer": "je"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "am",
            "word": "suis",
            "options": ["nous", "suis", "vous", "les"],
            "answer": "suis"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Select the correct meaning: 'no'?",
            "word": "non",
            "options": ["oui", "non", "moi", "jour"],
            "answer": "non"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'maybe'",
            "word": "peut-être",
            "options": ["oui", "non", "moi", "peut-être"],
            "answer": "peut-être"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "intermediate": {
     "section1": {
        "sectionDescription": "greetings",
        "questions": [
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which one of these is 'thank you'?",
            "word": "merci",
            "options": ["bonjour", "oui", "merci", "salut"],
            "answer": "merci"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "Please: 'S'il vous ___",
            "word": "plaît",
            "options": ["rein", "plait", "oui", "non"],
            "answer": "plaît"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which one of these is 'nice to meet you'?",
            "word": "enchanté(e)",
            "options": ["merci", "oui", "enchantée", "plait"],
            "answer": "enchanté(e)"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Select the correct meaning: 'welcome'?",
            "word": "bienvenue",
            "options": ["merci", "oui", "enchantée", "bienvenue"],
            "answer": "bienvenue"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "good day",
            "word": "bonne journée",
            "options": ["merci", "bonne journée", "bienvenue", "salut"],
            "answer": "bonne journée"
          }
        ]
      },
     "section2": {
        "sectionDescription": "everydayWords",
        "questions": [
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "The day",
            "word": "le jour",
            "options": ["le jour", "la nuit", "une fille", "je"],
            "answer": "le jour"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "garçon __ fille.",
            "word": "et",
            "options": ["et", "un", "une", "suis"],
            "answer": "et"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'house'",
            "word": "maison",
            "options": ["jour", "maison", "livre", "école"],
            "answer": "maison"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Select the correct meaning: 'work'?",
            "word": "travail",
            "options": ["maison", "livre", "travail", "jour"],
            "answer": "travail"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'store'",
            "word": "magasin",
            "options": ["magasin", "maison", "livre", "école"],
            "answer": "magasin"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'book'",
            "word": "livre",
            "options": ["magasin", "maison", "livre", "école"],
            "answer": "livre"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'boy'",
            "word": "garçon",
            "options": ["garçon", "fille", "femme", "homme"],
            "answer": "garçon"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'girl'",
            "word": "fille",
            "options": ["garçon", "fille", "femme", "homme"],
            "answer": "fille"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'man'",
            "word": "homme",
            "options": ["garçon", "fille", "femme", "homme"],
            "answer": "homme"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'woman'",
            "word": "femme",
            "options": ["garçon", "fille", "femme", "homme"],
            "answer": "femme"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "advanced": {
      "section1": {
        "sectionDescription": "greetings",
        "questions": [
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which one of these is 'see you later'?",
            "word": "à plus tard",
            "options": ["à plus tard", "bonne journée", "bienvenue", "salut"],
            "answer": "à plus tard"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "Excuse me Rhoda!. __ Rhoda!",
            "word": "excusez-moi",
            "options": ["à plus tard", "bienvenue", "excusez-moi", "merci"],
            "answer": "excusez-moi"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which one of these is 'see you tommorrow'?",
            "word": "à demain",
            "options": ["merci", "bienvenue", "à demain", "à plus tard"],
            "answer": "à demain"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Select the correct meaning: 'journey'?",
            "word": "voyage",
            "options": ["travail", "magasin", "bonne journée", "voyage"],
            "answer": "voyage"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Write it in French, 'safe journey'",
            "word": "bon voyage",
            "options": ["bon nuit", "bonsoir", "travail", "bon voyage"],
            "answer": "bon voyage"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which one of these is a'car'?",
            "word": "voiture",
            "options": ["chat", "chien", "voiture", "tableau"],
            "answer": "voiture"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Weather",
            "word": "temp",
            "options": ["temp", "chien", "voiture", "chat"],
            "answer": "temp"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "to go",
            "word": "aller",
            "options": ["aller", "avoir", "parler", "dire"],
            "answer": "aller"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "to have",
            "word": "avoir",
            "options": ["aller", "avoir", "parler", "dire"],
            "answer": "avoir"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "to say",
            "word": "dire",
            "options": ["aller", "avoir", "parler", "dire"],
            "answer": "dire"
          }

        ]
      },
     "section2": {
        "sectionDescription": "everydayWords",
        "questions": [
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "To eat",
            "word": "manger",
            "options": ["aller", "manger", "parler", "dire"],
            "answer": "manger"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "__ es Sam!",
            "word": "tu",
            "options": ["tu", "nous", "vous", "ils"],
            "answer": "tu"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'to speak'",
            "word": "parler",
            "options": ["aller", "avoir", "parler", "dire"],
            "answer": "parler"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Select the correct meaning: 'to be'?",
            "word": "être",
            "options": ["être", "avoir", "parler", "dire"],
            "answer": "être"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'to want'",
            "word": "vouloir",
            "options": ["aller", "avoir", "parler", "vouloir"],
            "answer": "vouloir"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "petite",
            "word": "small",
            "options": ["larger", "big", "small", "pretty"],
            "answer": "small"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "bad",
            "word": "mauvais",
            "options": ["petite", "mauvais", "jeune", "bon"],
            "answer": "mauvais"
          },
          
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "young",
            "word": "jeune",
            "options": ["petite", "mauvais", "jeune", "bon"],
            "answer": "jeune"
          },
          
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "beautiful",
            "word": "beau",
            "options": ["beau", "mauvais", "jeune", "viens"],
            "answer": "beau"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'the orange'?",
            "word": "orange",
            "options": ["orange", "papaya", "avocado", "pizza"],
            "answer": "orange"
          }
        ]
      }
    }
  },
  "sentenceBuilding": {
    "greetings": [
      {
        "questionType": "mcq",
        "question": "Which one of these is 'hello'?",
        "word": "salut",
        "options": ["bonjour", "oui", "merci", "salut"],
        "answer": "salut"
      },
      {
        "questionType": "fill-in",
        "question": "__ Rhoda!",
        "word": "salut",
        "options": ["bonjour", "oui", "salut", "merci"],
        "answer": "salut"
      }
    ],
    "everydayWords": [
      {
        "questionType": "mcq",
        "question": "Which one of these is 'hello'?",
        "word": "salut",
        "options": ["bonjour", "oui", "merci", "salut"],
        "answer": "salut"
      },
      {
        "questionType": "fill-in",
        "question": "__ Rhoda!",
        "word": "salut",
        "options": ["bonjour", "oui", "salut", "merci"],
        "answer": "salut"
      }
    ]
  },
  "dialogueSimulation": {
    "greetings": [
      {
        "questionType": "mcq",
        "question": "Which one of these is 'hello'?",
        "word": "salut",
        "options": ["bonjour", "oui", "merci", "salut"],
        "answer": "salut"
      },
      {
        "questionType": "fill-in",
        "question": "__ Rhoda!",
        "word": "salut",
        "options": ["bonjour", "oui", "salut", "merci"],
        "answer": "salut"
      }
    ],
    "everydayWords": [
      {
        "questionType": "mcq",
        "question": "Which one of these is 'hello'?",
        "word": "salut",
        "options": ["bonjour", "oui", "merci", "salut"],
        "answer": "salut"
      },
      {
        "questionType": "fill-in",
        "question": "__ Rhoda!",
        "word": "salut",
        "options": ["bonjour", "oui", "salut", "merci"],
        "answer": "salut"
      }
    ]
  }
}
